Thank you for watching!
Yakanpa Idol
And the third one is talking.
I always liked to talk a lot.
But rather than talking to myself, I really liked talking to other people.
But since the fall of 2021, I've been the main personality on a radio show.
It's a group radio show.
I had a chance to be a main personality on a radio show.
And when I listened to the stories of the guests who came to the show...
I felt that idols were always in the spotlight.
They listen to us, don't they?
I thought it was very difficult to be on the listening side.
I thought that I could say that I like talking the most when I can listen to and accept what is being said.
I think it's very important for me to realize that in this job.
I see.
When it comes to talking about myself, I've been doing it for eight years, and I've gotten better at it.
But when guests came to the show and I had to turn it into my own thing, it was very difficult.
It was very difficult.
I tried to listen to my own broadcasts, but I thought I might not be able to listen to them this time.
I tried to listen to my own broadcasts, but there were times when I thought I might not be able to listen to them this time.
I didn't think I did very well, and there were times when I thought I might not be able to listen to it.
I thought it was a lot of fun.
But you're dealing with it properly, right?
No, no, no, that's a great way to face it.
It's nice. It's nice. It's nice.
Well, even if people don't get into it, even if the members don't get into it...
But you're doing it, right?
I thought it was great that you were in charge of MC until a little while ago, or you were in charge of the group.
Even before I became the MC, I had the impression that I was doing all the talking.
I had to do all the talking.
But now I feel that I don't have to be the MC.
I started to assign the MC duties to the various members.
I think I'm having a good time with everyone and the audience is enjoying the show.
I also feel a little more at ease.
Oh, I see.
I realized that I don't have to talk.
But I had the impression that you liked to talk.
Now that I've talked to you for the first time in a while...
I've been thinking about what we're talking about again.
I think we have a good way of looking at things and having a good conversation.
It's totally different from the old days.
But there is one thing I think I need to fix.
When I'm talking, I keep thinking about the future.
I sometimes lose track of what I'm talking about.
Marriage meeting? Is that so?
That's right.
It's okay when we're talking about a play or something, like now, when we're talking completely about the play.
Are you okay? I'm afraid you're talking out of your head right now.
I know this from the bottom of my heart.
I know this from the bottom of my heart, but sometimes in private, when I'm talking to my friends or my parents...
My mind just goes on and on and on.
I have so many things I want to talk about.
I have to be able to switch it up.
I have to be able to switch between them.
But I'm not like that at all.
I'm relatively that way myself.
I've got a lot of things I want to say, and I want to say them.
In five days, what? You're in Paris?
I'll be in Paris.
That's great.
Brought to you courtesy of Mr. Koffi.
Thank you very much.